<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>henry-rollins</title><link>https://www.kcrw.com/music/shows/henry-rollins</link><description>Henry Rollins hosts a mix of all kinds, from all over and all time.</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 22:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate><item><title>KCRW Broadcast 825</title><link>https://ondemand-media.kcrw.com/fdd/audio/download/kcrw/music/hr/KCRW-henry_rollins-kcrw_broadcast_825-250125.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Fanatic! I hope you had a great week and had a chance to listen to some music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You might have noticed we’ve been listening to a band called Horsegirl for the last few weeks. Their album Versions Of Modern Performance is really good. Thanks to Fanatic Denise for the heads up. Yesterday I was told the band has a new album slated for February. I went to Bandcamp and found this to be true. The preorder tracks sound really good. We’ll be getting into the album as soon as possible. &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>KCRW Broadcast 824</title><link>https://ondemand-media.kcrw.com/fdd/audio/download/kcrw/music/hr/KCRW-henry_rollins-kcrw_broadcast_824-250118.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Fanatic. I hope you had a good week. Hopefully the winds that have been feeding the fires in Southern California are pulling back and allowing firefighting personnel to make advances against the flames.  &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>KCRW Broadcast 822</title><link>https://ondemand-media.kcrw.com/fdd/audio/download/kcrw/music/hr/KCRW-henry_rollins-kcrw_broadcast_822-250111.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Fanatic. I hope no matter where you are that you’re safe and in good condition. I can’t explain how sorry I am for what has been lost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; We hope you enjoy tonight’s gathering of tracks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Thank you so much for tuning in. Be safe and stay Fanatic.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>KCRW Broadcast 821</title><link>https://ondemand-media.kcrw.com/fdd/audio/download/kcrw/music/hr/KCRW-henry_rollins-kcrw_broadcast_821-251228.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Fanatic! It’s our last show for the year. Engineer X, Engineer Am-Rock and I would like to thank you so much for tuning in. We hope we kept things interesting and that you will stay with us as we go fanatically into 2025.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just my opinion, but I don’t think there’s ever been a time when music wasn’t essential to getting through the challenges life throws at us, seemingly at every turn. That being said, I think music becomes more of an asset in certain times. It keeps us inspired, curious and encouraged. I have no crystal ball for this kind of thing but it very well could be that we will be leaning on music pretty hard next year. Good thing for us, there’s a lot of good music to be heard and we’re going to listen to a lot of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; We hope you’ll find tonight’s show to be a good soundtrack for whatever you’re up to as 2024 draws to a close. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, Engineer X and I started putting the finishing touches on our first show for next year. It’s going to be a great one. Until then, keep jamming and STAY FANATIC!!! &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>KCRW Broadcast 820</title><link>https://ondemand-media.kcrw.com/fdd/audio/download/kcrw/music/hr/KCRW-henry_rollins-kcrw_broadcast_820-241221.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Fanatic! I hope you had a great week and had a chance to listen to some music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>KCRW Broadcast 819</title><link>https://ondemand-media.kcrw.com/fdd/audio/download/kcrw/music/hr/KCRW-henry_rollins-kcrw_broadcast_819-241214.mp3</link><description>&lt;p style="text-align: left;"&gt;Fanatic! I hope you had a great and music-filled week. For the most part, I’ve been tied to my desk doing a lot of scanning, proofreading, editing, and writing. I’ve also been able to get some records played. These are but a few.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>KCRW Broadcast 818</title><link>https://ondemand-media.kcrw.com/fdd/audio/download/kcrw/music/hr/KCRW-henry_rollins-kcrw_broadcast_818-241207.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Fanatic! I hope you had a great week. I’ve been checking out some good records.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>KCRW Broadcast 817</title><link>https://ondemand-media.kcrw.com/fdd/audio/download/kcrw/music/hr/KCRW-henry_rollins-kcrw_broadcast_817-241130.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Fanatic! I understand that the Thanksgiving holiday can sometimes be intense for some people who have to gather with members of their family who they might have strong disagreements with, spend hours with them, ending with a grand meal set at a table before all parties are allowed to stagger away fuming and go back to their respective dwellings. The angry parties, all swearing vengeance, promise to do it all over again around this time next year. Sounds crazy to me but humans are highly complex creatures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Tonight’s show is ever so slightly conceptual. If you notice, Generation X tracks start both hours. We are doing this because it is Billy Idol's birthday. Happy birthday, Billy!&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>